- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
All right, Karen.
好吧，凯伦。
I'm off to go shopping.
我要去购物了。
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
Oh!
哦！
- Uh... ew!
- 呃...呃！
What is that?
那是什么？
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Ahh!
啊！
[groans]
[呻吟]
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
Huh?
- Hey, over here.
啊？
- 嘿，在这里。
[jazzy music]
[爵士乐]
- So, uh, you got the goods?
- 那么，呃，你拿到货了吗？
- Of course.
- 当然。
I always deliver.
我总是送货。
- Hee-hee.
- 嘻嘻。
Eee!
哎呀！
- Pleasure doing
business with you.
- 做事的乐趣
与您开展业务。
- Likewise, my shady friend.
- 同样，我的阴暗朋友。
So same time next...
那么接下来的同一时间...
[groans]
[呻吟]
[accordion music]
[手风琴音乐]
[groans]
[呻吟]
I'm here for the formula.
我是来求公式的
Hand it over, and nobody gets...
交给别人吧，没有人能得到...
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Ew.
- 呃。
I seem to have stepped in
some revolting substance.
我仿佛已经踏入
一些令人反感的物质。
No matter.
不管。
- Ouch.
- 哎哟。
Ouch.
哎哟。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Honey, I'm home.
亲爱的，我回来了。
- Tough day at work, dear?
- 亲爱的，今天工作辛苦吗？
- Yes.
- 是的。
Everybody stepped on me again.
大家又踩到我身上了。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Well, I know what'll
cheer up my little man.
好吧，我知道会发生什么
让我的小男人高兴起来。
Let's dance those blues away.
让我们一起跳舞消除那些忧郁吧。
- Oh, boy!
- 哦，孩子！
[air horn blares]
[气喇叭声]
- Oh, yeah.
- 哦，是的。
Go, Sheldon.
走吧，谢尔顿。
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
- You were right, Karen,
I feel better already.
- 你是对的，凯伦，
我已经感觉好多了。
I've got boogie fever!
我得了布吉热！
[groans]
[呻吟]
- We haven't danced like
this since our wedding night.
-我们没有像这样跳舞
这是从我们新婚之夜开始的。
- [laughs] Whoo!
- [笑] 哇！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- [vocalizing]
- [发声]
- Plankton?
- 浮游生物？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Pardon me.
对不起。
Plankton?
浮游生物？
Plankton,
are you there, sweetie?
浮游生物，
你在吗，亲爱的？
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Plankton?
- 浮游生物？
[grunts]
There you are.
[咕哝]
你就在那里。
At least part of you.
至少是你的一部分。
- That's it!
- 就是这样！
I'm not getting
stepped on anymore.
我没有得到
不再踩了。
Take me to my lab.
带我去我的实验室。
- Sure.
- 当然。
But let's find
the rest of you first.
但我们要找到
你们其他人先。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
[bell dings]
[铃声]
[grunts] Foot Deterrent,
Version 1.1, commence test.
[咕噜声]脚威慑，
1.1版本，开始测试。
[groans]
[呻吟]
Not quite there.
不完全在那里。
- Foot Deterrent, laser thingy.
- 脚步威慑，激光之物。
[sighs] Might as well
get this over with.
[叹气]也可以
把这件事结束吧。
[laser pings]
[激光脉冲]
[machine hisses]
[机器嘶嘶声]
What?
什么？
Yes.
是的。
I'm invincible!
我无敌了！
Ohh-ohh-ohh-ohh.
哦哦哦哦。
Ah!
啊!
[laser blasts]
[激光爆炸]
Ow.
噢。
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
All right, time for a field test
好的，是时候进行实地测试了
in T-minus 3, 2, 1.
在 T-减 3, 2, 1 中。
- Huh?
[laser blasts]
- 啊？
[激光爆炸]
- Hmm.
- 唔。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- My foot!
- 我的脚！
Ouch.
哎哟。
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
Take that,
you high-stepping ham!
就拿那个来说，
你这个高高在上的火腿！
Huh?
啊？
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- Oh, boy.
- 哦，男孩。
Time to stop
those big metal stompers.
是时候停下来了
那些大金属踩踏器。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
Hmm?
唔？
[grunting]
Hwah!
[咕噜声]
哇！
Hee-yah!
嘿呀！
[laser blasts]
[激光爆炸]
- Plankton, what in
tarnation are you doing?
- 浮游生物，什么在
你在做什么？
You almost barbecued
my dang paw.
你差点就烤了
我的爪子。
- Duh.
- 呃。
That was the point.
这就是重点。
But hey, what was that
"hiyah" stuff you just did?
但是，嘿，那是什么？
你刚刚做了“嗨”的事情吗？
- Well, that was just good,
old-fashioned self-defense.
- 嗯，那很好，
老式的自卫。
You know, karate.
你知道，空手道。
Looks like you could use
a little self-defense too.
看起来你可以使用
也有一点自卫。
Why don't you swing by my dome
so I can show you some moves?
你为什么不在我的圆顶附近荡来荡去
所以我可以给你展示一些动作？
- Anything to stop the stomping.
- 任何可以阻止跺脚的东西。
Hmm?
唔？
- Huh?
- 啊？
[sighs]
[叹气]
[mystical music]
[神秘音乐]
- All right,
Plankton, come on out.
- 好吧，
浮游生物，出来吧。
- Mm.
- 毫米。
I make this gi look good.
我让这件道服看起来不错。
- Now bow to your sensei.
- 现在向你的老师鞠躬。
- Plankton bows to no one.
- 浮游生物不向任何人低头。
- Huh?
- Hiyah.
- 啊？
-嗨。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- Good.
- 好的。
Now we may begin.
现在我们可以开始了。
We must first gauge your
current level of self-defense.
我们必须首先衡量你的
目前的自卫水平。
Think fast!
快想想吧！
- Think what?
- 想想什么？
Ouch!
哎哟!
Now I know why
they call it a sneaker.
现在我知道为什么了
他们称之为运动鞋。
- Maybe something
a little gentler.
- 也许有什么
温柔一点。
- [grunting] Whoa!
- [咕哝] 哇！
I can't flip like you.
我不能像你一样翻转。
Only flop.
只能失败。
- OK.
- 好的。
How 'bout these?
这些怎么样？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Ouch!
- 哎呀！
- Huh.
- 嗯。
Seems like you lack
the fundamentals.
看来你缺乏
基本面。
What you need
is some basic training.
你需要什么
是一些基础训练。
- [grunts] Okey-dokey,
furry lady.
- [咕哝] 好吧，
毛茸茸的女士。
[funky music]
[时髦音乐]
Hyah, hyah, hyah, hyah, hyah!
哈、哈、哈、哈、哈！
Ow.
噢。
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Ah!
[咕哝]
啊！
[grunts]
Ha-ha!
[咕哝]
哈哈！
Augh!
啊啊！
Heh-heh-heh.
呵呵。
Hiyah!
嗨！
Hee-hee.
嘻嘻。
[glass squeaking]
[玻璃吱吱作响]
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[mystical music]
[神秘音乐]
- Now that you've
mastered the basics,
- 现在你已经
掌握了基础知识，
I reckon you're ready to
spar with a real partner.
我想你已经准备好了
与真正的伙伴进行对决。
- Hi, Plankton!
- 嗨，浮游生物！
- SpongeBob?
- 海绵宝宝？
- Don't you worry.
- 别担心。
I'll go easy on ya.
我会轻松对待你的。
Foam sparring boots.
泡沫陪练靴。
- I can't promise
I'll do the same.
-我不能保证
我也会这样做。
- Bow to your opponents.
- 向你的对手鞠躬。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Now fight!
- 现在战斗！
- Wah!
- 哇！
- Hmm?
- Yah!
- 唔？
- 啊！
- Ah!
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- That was pretty
good, Plankton.
- 那很漂亮
好，浮游生物。
But remember to
keep your guard up.
但请记住
保持警惕。
- It's no use.
- 这没有用。
I'm just too small to
avoid being stepped on.
我只是太小了
避免被踩到。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
But in karate, your
greatest weakness may also
但在空手道中，你的
最大的弱点也可能是
be your greatest strength.
成为你最大的力量。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
But in "rea-li-tay," that
doesn't make any sense!
但在“real-li-tay”中，
没有任何意义！
- Allow me to demonstrate.
- 请允许我演示一下。
SpongeBob,
give me the old roundhouse.
海绵宝宝，
把旧的圆屋给我。
- Wah!
- 哇！
- Your opponent's
momentum can be used...
- 你对手的
可以使用动量...
- Huh?
- 啊？
[groans]
[呻吟]
- against them,
no matter your size.
- 反对他们，
无论您的身材如何。
You OK, SpongeBob?
你还好吗，海绵宝宝？
- I would bow to you If I could.
- 如果可以的话，我会向你鞠躬。
Ouch.
哎哟。
- That was incredible!
- 太不可思议了！
Let me try.
让我试试。
- Visualize the technique.
- 可视化该技术。
Grab, twist,
and let gravity do the rest.
抓住、扭转、
让重力完成剩下的工作。
- Shut up.
- 住口。
You're distracting me.
你分散了我的注意力。
[mystical music]
[神秘音乐]
[inhales and exhales]
[吸气和呼气]
- Hwah!
- 哇！
[funky music]
[时髦音乐]
- Hiyah!
- Ugh!
-嗨！
- 呃！
- I did it!
- 我做到了！
In your face, feet!
在你的脸上，脚上！
[gong resounds]
[锣声响起]
- Congratulations, Plankton.
- 恭喜你，浮游生物。
But remember, this
technique is to be used
但请记住，这
技术是要使用的
strictly for self-defense.
严格出于自卫目的。
- Oh, of course, Sensei Sandy.
- 哦，当然，桑迪老师。
Uh, wink.
呃，眨眼。
Buh-bye!
再见！
[laughs]
[笑]
- Uh, Sandy, could you give
me a ride to the hospital?
- 呃，桑迪，你能给吗
搭车送我去医院吗？
- Whoops!
- 哎呀！
Oh, sure, SpongeBob. Heh-heh.
哦，当然，海绵宝宝。呵呵。
- All right,
who's looking to rumble?
- 好吧，
谁在寻找隆隆声？
Huh? You!
啊？你！
- [slurping]
- [发出声音]
Heh-heh.
呵呵。
Hiyah!
嗨！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
What unexplained
force of nature?
什么无法解释
自然的力量？
Ah!
啊!
- I feel so powerful!
- 我感觉自己好强大！
[elephant trumpeting]
[大象的喇叭声]
And I can't help but
use that power for evil!
我情不自禁
利用这种力量作恶！
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
Oh, Krabsy, hyah, I'm home!
哦，克拉布西，嘿，我回来了！
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
Oh!
哦！
- Whoa, whoa! Oh!
- 哇，哇！哦！
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- [cackles]
No one can stop me now.
- [咯咯笑]
现在没有人能阻止我了。
That secret formula
will be mine!
那个秘密配方
将是我的！
- Hmm.
- Hiyah!
- 唔。
-嗨！
- Whoa, whoa! Ugh!
- 哇，哇！啊!
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
- Plankton?
- 浮游生物？
- No, not Plankton.
- 不，不是浮游生物。
[all shouting]
[大家大喊]
[alarm blaring]
[警报声]
- I made it.
- 我做到了。
Huh?
啊？
Security ninjas?
安全忍者？
Heh.
Krabs thinks of everything.
呵呵。
蟹老板什么都会想到。
Bring it on!
来吧！
[funky music]
[时髦音乐]
♪ ♪
- Whah!
- 哇！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Knock, knock.
敲，敲。
- [grumbles] Plankton!
- [抱怨]浮游生物！
How did you get past
me security ninjas?
你是怎么过去的
我是安全忍者？
- With the art of karate.
- 空手道艺术。
Now that I can defend myself,
your feet are all doomed!
现在我可以保护自己了
你的脚就完蛋了！
- Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
- 啊哈哈哈哈哈哈！
- Oh, you won't be laughing
once I use my ultimate
-哦，你不会笑的
一旦我使用我的终极
foot-stomping finisher!
跺脚终结者！
[accordion music]
[手风琴音乐]
- Bad news for you, Plankton.
- 对你来说是个坏消息，浮游生物。
I don't have any feet.
我没有脚。
- You what?
- 你什么？
[foghorn blaring]
[雾号鸣响]
Just my luck, I guess.
我想这只是我的运气。
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Hee-hee!
- 嘻嘻！
The old familiar sting
of "de-feet," aye?
古老熟悉的刺痛
“失脚”，是吗？
[laughs]
[笑]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
Six to eight weeks before I can
attack the Krusty Krab again.
六到八周后我就可以
再次攻击蟹堡王。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
At least I'm not
in traction anymore.
至少我不是
不再有牵引力。
Augh!
啊啊！
- Oh, boy!
- 哦，孩子！
Only six to eight weeks before
I can work
仅六到八周前
我可以工作
at the Krusty Krab again!
又来蟹堡啦！
- Ouch!
- 哎呀！
Karate is a pain in the... ouch!
空手道是一种痛苦……哎呀！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
- [笑]
♪ ♪
- Excuse me, Miss.
- 对不起，小姐。
Is this seat taken?
这个座位有人吗？
- It is now, Sailor.
- 现在就是了，水手。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Mm...
毫米...
- Hmm?
- 唔？
[bell rings]
[铃声响起]
- Three bells?
- 三响铃？
It's lunchtime!
午餐时间到了！
Better get some food!
最好吃点东西！
- Oh, Fondue Man!
- 哦，火锅人！
- Huh?
- 啊？
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿，嘿，嘿。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
Oh.
哦。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Ooh.
- 哦。
Ah.
啊。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
Hmm?
唔？
Mm.
毫米。
Heh-heh-heh-heh.
嘿嘿嘿嘿。
[accordion music]
[手风琴音乐]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
- Mwah.
- 哇。
Hmm.
唔。
Mm?
毫米？
Hmm.
唔。
A 5 cent tip?
5分钱小费？
Thanks a lot, Mister.
非常感谢，先生。
Hmph!
哼！
[wheels squeaking]
[车轮吱吱作响]
- Ah, fondue.
- 啊，火锅。
The perfect food
for a beach date.
完美的食物
去海滩约会。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Oh.
哦。
- Uh, OK.
OK.
- 呃，好的。
好的。
- Oh.
- OK.
- 哦。
- 好的。
No.
Oh...
不。
哦...
- Oh.
Ooh.
- 哦。
哦。
[gulps]
[吞咽]
- Um.
- 嗯。
- Oh.
- 哦。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Mmm-mmm.
- 嗯嗯。
- ♪ Na-na-na-na-na ♪
- ♪ 娜娜娜娜娜娜 ♪
[teeth grinding]
[磨牙]
- ♪ Na-na-na ♪
- ♪ 娜娜娜 ♪
- [gulps]
- [吞咽]
♪ ♪
[glasses clink]
[眼镜叮当作响]
[both gulping]
[两人都咽了一口口水]
[seagulls squawking]
[海鸥的叫声]
- [groans] Whoo-hoo!
- [呻吟] 呼呼！
Now, that was a meal.
现在，那是一顿饭。
What do you say to a romantic
dip in the goo, my sweet?
你对浪漫的人说什么
浸入粘液中，亲爱的？
- Well, I suppose I could
wash off some of this cheese.
- 嗯，我想我可以
洗掉一些奶酪。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Whoo-hoo!
Oh!
- 呼呼！
哦！
- Oh!
Oh.
- 哦！
哦。
- Huh?
- 啊？
Ah!
啊!
- [yells]
- [大喊]
- [laughs] Oh!
- [笑]哦！
- [yelling]
- [大喊]
- Eugene!
- 尤金！
- The undertow's got me!
- 暗流抓住了我！
Whoa!
哇！
- Help!
- 帮助！
- Huh?
- 啊？
Rump in a riptide!
臀部激流！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[whirring]
[呼呼]
[water splashing]
[水花四溅]
I gotcha, bro.
我明白了，兄弟。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- [retches, mumbles]
- [干呕，咕哝]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Yay!
- 耶！
- Thank you, Larry.
- 谢谢你，拉里。
- Ooh.
- Mwah!
- 哦。
- 哇！
- Hmm.
- Thank you!
- 唔。
- 谢谢你！
Thank you!
谢谢你！
- [retches]
- [干呕]
- Eugene, don't try to talk.
- 尤金，别试图说话。
I'd better take you home.
我最好带你回家。
Bye, Larry.
再见，拉里。
Thanks again.
再次感谢。
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Larry's always
ready to step in.
- 拉里总是
准备介入。
[bell dings]
[铃声]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- [yowling]
- [嚎叫]
- I'm telling you, boy-o,
that kiss, that wave...
- 我告诉你，男孩，
那个吻，那个挥手……
I'm losing me sweet Puff
to a shiny-shelled boy toy!
我快要失去我可爱的泡芙了
一个闪亮的外壳男孩玩具！
- Well, maybe your
eyes were confused.
- 嗯，也许你的
眼神迷茫。
[laughs]
[笑]
- No.
- 不。
She loved Larry's muscles.
她喜欢拉里的肌肉。
She's sick of this
old sack of fondue.
她厌倦了这个
老麻袋火锅。
- Look, Mr. K.,
I'm sure Mrs. Puff
- 看，K先生，
我确信泡芙女士
loves you for who you are,
not how many muscles you have.
爱你本来的样子
不是你有多少肌肉。
- Look.
- 看。
Look, boy.
看，男孩。
This farmer's tan, this
flabby shell, so undefined.
这个农民晒黑了，这个
松软的外壳，所以未定义。
See the realities of middle
age on an all-fondue diet!
看看中层的真实情况
全火锅饮食的年龄！
Look away!
- Ah!
看开！
- 啊！
- No crab should look like this!
- 螃蟹不应该是这样的！
[bouncy music]
[轻快的音乐]
There's only one option, boy-o.
只有一个选择，男孩。
I gotta get in shape
before me next date.
我必须保持身材
在我下次约会之前。
And you're gonna help!
你会帮忙的！
- [squealing]
- [尖叫声]
That crustaceous hunk doesn't
know who I am or why I'm
那个硬壳大块头不
知道我是谁或为什么我是
here, boy-o.
在这里，小伙子。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- Go, go, go!
- 去！去！去！
Yeah, yeah!
是啊是啊！
Unh, unh, unh!
呃呃呃！
Go, go, go, go!
走，走，走，走！
Sweat!
汗！
- This was a mistake.
- 这是一个错误。
Abandoned gym!
废弃的健身房！
- You can do this, Mr. Krabs.
- 你可以做到的，蟹老板。
Do it for Mrs. Puff.
为泡芙夫人做吧。
[grunts]
Huh?
[咕哝]
啊？
- Oh, you're right.
- 哦，你说得对。
I'll do it for Puff.
我会为泡芙做的。
Oh!
哦！
- Welcome to my
temple of the bods.
- 欢迎来到我的
身体的寺庙。
- Save the sales pitch.
I got this.
- 保存销售宣传。
我明白了。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[both groans]
[两人都呻吟]
- You know,
that's actually for...
- 你知道，
这其实是为了...
- Whoops.
Heh-heh.
- 哎呀。
呵呵。
Finished me reps.
完成了我的代表。
Hmm.
唔。
OK.
好的。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- I can show you how to...
- OK.
- 我可以告诉你如何...
- 好的。
Got me heart rate up.
Ya-ho.
让我心跳加快。
雅浩。
- Uh, Mr. Krabs?
- 呃，蟹老板？
- Never heard of him.
- 从没听说过他。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[mumbling]
[咕哝]
- Must be shy about
his first day.
- 一定是害羞了
他的第一天。
If you want to work out, I'd
be happy to help train you.
如果你想锻炼的话我会
很乐意帮助培训您。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Heh, heh.
呵呵。
Yeah, maybe I
could use a few pointers.
是的，也许我
可以使用一些指针。
- Let's just try lifting
some free weights.
- 让我们尝试举重
一些自由重量。
- Look, Larry, I'm doing it!
- 看，拉里，我正在做！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Wah!
哇！
- [groans] Sponge...
- [呻吟]海绵……
- [grunts]
- Huh?
- [咕哝]
- 啊？
Hey!
- [grunting]
嘿！
- [咕哝]
[laughs]
[笑]
- No stealing
the free weights, bro.
- 禁止偷窃
自由重量，兄弟。
- Well, are they free or not?
- 嗯，它们免费吗？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
I've never met anyone
as workout-averse as you.
我从未见过任何人
和你一样厌恶锻炼。
I just don't know
how to motivate you.
我只是不知道
如何激励你。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
I know how to motivate him.
我知道如何激励他。
♪ ♪
Huh? Huh?
啊？啊？
- Ooh.
- 哦。
Money, money, money,
money, money, money.
钱，钱，钱，
钱，钱，钱。
[grunts]
Money!
[咕哝]
钱！
Money!
- Whoa.
钱！
- 哇哦。
Nice trick, little dude.
好技巧，小家伙。
- That's nothing.
- 那没什么。
You should see how I get
him to take his pills.
你应该看看我是如何得到的
他服药。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[cash register dings]
[收银机叮叮声]
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[cash register dinging]
[收银机叮叮声]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[laughs]
[笑]
Yeah!
是的！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- Whew.
- 呼。
That was one heck of a workout.
那真是一次艰苦的锻炼。
Time to see what 168
straight hours of exercise
是时候看看什么了 168
连续几个小时的锻炼
does to the body.
对身体有影响。
- Ahh.
- 啊。
[gasps]
[喘气]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- Hey!
- 嘿！
What's the deal, Larry?
这是怎么回事，拉里？
Why ain't I ripped?
为啥我没撕？
- Fitness is a
lifelong journey, bro.
- 健身是一个
一生的旅程，兄弟。
Can't change your
physique in a week.
无法改变你的
一周内体质。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- [grunts] Ah.
- [咕哝]啊。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
See you bros in the sauna.
兄弟们桑拿见。
- Hmm?
- 唔？
[groans]
[呻吟]
No one can change
their physique, eh?
没有人可以改变
他们的体质吧？
Hee-hee-hee-hee.
嘻嘻嘻。
[laid back music]
[悠闲的音乐]
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
Huh?
啊？
[engine revving]
[发动机转速]
- Ha-ha.
- 哈哈。
[laughs]
[笑]
[grunts]
Ha!
[咕哝]
哈！
- Ooh? Ahh.
- 哦？啊。
Oh.
哦。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
♪ ♪
- Hey there, ma'am.
- 嘿，女士。
Is this beach taken?
这个海滩被占领了吗？
- Oh, my.
- 哦，天哪。
Eugene, you're so well-defined.
尤金，你的定义非常明确。
Eugene?
尤金？
[together]
Yeah! Ha-ha! Yeah!
[一起]
是啊！哈哈！是的！
- Take a look.
- 看一下。
These are called gains, people.
人们，这些被称为收益。
Yeah.
是的。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Hmm.
- 唔。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Ah!
- 啊！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Nice pecs, Mr. Krabs.
蟹老板，胸肌不错。
- We love you!
- 我们爱你！
- Wow.
We love you.
- 哇。
我们爱你。
- Strongest crab in the world!
- 世界上最强的螃蟹！
I fear no man!
我不怕任何人！
- [scoffs]
- [嘲笑]
- Krabs!
- 螃蟹！
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
[all gasp]
- Larry?
[全都喘气]
- 拉里？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- I'm going to crack you
right out of my shell, bro.
-我要打碎你
就在我的壳里，兄弟。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Mr. Krabs, looking good!
蟹老板，看起来不错！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- Was that Larry?
- 那是拉里吗？
He must have stopped working
out for a few minutes.
他一定已经停止工作了
出去几分钟。
- Ahh!
- 啊！
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Fondue?
火锅？
At the beach?
在海滩？
Whoa!
哇！
[groans] Oh, oh, oh, oh!
[呻吟]哦，哦，哦，哦！
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦，哦！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- Larry's in trouble.
- 拉里有麻烦了。
- Someone save him!
- 谁来救救他！
- Who will lifeguard
the lifeguards?
- 谁来担任救生员
救生员？
- [whimpers] Huh?
- [呜咽] 嗯？
Fondue Man!
火锅人！
- Ah!
- Yeah!
- 啊！
- 是的！
Yeah!
是的！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Uh, OK.
呃，好吧。
- Ouch!
- 哎呀！
Whoa!
哇！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
[gasping]
Ohh.
[喘气]
哦。
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- Oh, yeah!
- 哦，是的！
Ha-ha.
哈哈。
That's right,
saving the day over here.
没错，
在这里拯救一天。
What do you think of
me now, Puffykins?
你觉得怎么样
现在是我吗，普菲金斯？
Your old Krabsy
is quite the hero.
你的老克拉布西
是相当的英雄。
Hiyah!
嗨！
- Oh, puh-lease.
- 哦，租借。
I'm not into muscle-bound,
self-centered jerks.
我不喜欢肌肉发达，
以自我为中心的混蛋。
- Heh-heh.
- 呵呵。
What's that?
那是什么？
- I like my boys a little
soft around the edges.
- 我有点喜欢我的男孩们
边缘柔软。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Mwah.
- 哇。
- Ah-ha-ha-ha.
- 啊哈哈哈。
Hmm.
唔。
- That's why Larry and I
have a beach date tomorrow.
- 这就是为什么拉里和我
明天去海滩约会。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Ha-ha!
- 哈哈！
Larry loves beach dates.
拉里喜欢海滩约会。
- Beach date?
- 海滩约会？
Wait!
等待！
I was kidding!
我开玩笑的！
The muscles were just a ruse.
肌肉只是一个诡计。
Puffy!
蓬松！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[all murmuring]
[大家窃窃私语]
- [grunts] See!
- [咕哝]看！
Ha-ha.
Oh.
哈哈。
哦。
Ah!
啊!
Puffykins, I'm soft.
普菲金斯，我很温柔。
- [sobbing]
- [抽泣]